Wolf, Benjamin H. Additional Arbitration Files 5539
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 78-80 New York State Department of Correctional Services vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 82, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- 78-81 U.S. Postal Service vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  10/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits. Settled.
- 78-82 Jersey City State College vs. Mildred Perry, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  8/78. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 78-83 Owens-Illinois, Lilly Division vs. International Printing and Graphic Communications Union, Local 447, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  10/16/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Change of Operations.
- 78-84 Brunswick-Fairlawn Lanes vs. International Longshoremen's Association, Local 1964, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  12/5/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Rates of Pay--Classification of Job--Wage Differential.
- 78-85 Trans World Airline vs. Air Line Pilots Association, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  9/78. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 78-86 New York State Office of Mental Health vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  10/3/78. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Arbitrability--Timeliness.
- 78-87 Miller Brewing Company vs. International Association of Machinists (IAM), District 137, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  10/78. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 78-88 Staten Island Rapid Transit Operating Authority vs. New York City Transit Authority, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  10/23/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents, Exhibits. Issue: Strikes--Breach of No-Strike Clause.
- 78-89 New York State Office of Mental Retardation vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- 78-90 New York State Office of Mental Health vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- 78-91 Dairylea Cooperative, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 338, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  3/79. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Classification of Jobs--Bargaining Units.
- 78-92 Ward Leonard Electric Company vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), Local 475, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  7/19/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, TR. Issue: Working Conditions--Management Rights--Pay Day.
- 78-93 Exxon Research and Engineering Company vs. Independent Laboratory Employees Union, Incorporated, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  4/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits. Settled.
- 78-94 Staley Elevator Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), Local 463, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  11/9/78. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits. Issue: Vacation--Rates of Pay--Increase.
- 78-95 William Patterson College, State of New Jersey vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  6/30/80. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Promotion--Discrimination.
- 78-96 State of New York Office of Mental Retardation vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  11/78. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 78-97 Acme Hamilton Manufacturing Corporation vs. United Rubber Workers, Local 95, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  12/78. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-98 Kean College, State of New Jersey vs. American Federation of Teachers (AFT), Local 2187, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  11/30/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Promotion--Management Rights; Union Representatives--Right To Information.
- 78-99 State of New York Office of Mental Health vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1979 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  1/79. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 78-100 New York City Off-Track Betting Corporation vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Local 2021, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  11/27/78. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Demotion--Carelessness and Negligence--Plant Rules.
- 78-102 State of New Jersey vs. State Troopers NCO (Non-Commissioned Officers'?) Association of New Jersey, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  8/78. (No Award), Routine Correspondence.
- 78-103 Johnson and Johnson vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Local 630, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  12/78. Routine Correspondence, Agreements. Settled.
- 78-104 New York Telephone Company vs. International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 94-94A, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  4/4/79. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Contracting Out--Layoff.
- 78-105 U.S. Trucking Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 814, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  11/78. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 78-106 Exxon Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 877, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  10/10/79. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Agreements. Issue: Discharge--Absences--Unauthorized.
- 78-107 New York State Department of Correctional Services vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 82, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  12/11/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge--Improper Personal Conduct--Concealed Weapon.
- 78-108 New York State Office of Mental Health vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  12/11/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Improper Personal Conduct--Assault.
- 78-109 Tenneco Chemicals vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 8570, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  12/22/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Quits--Voluntary.
- 78-110 State of New Jersey vs. New Jersey State Police, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 17a)
  8/18/82. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Promotion--Arbitrability.
- 78-111 State of New Jersey vs. New Jersey State Troopers, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  12/78. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 78-112 Globe Union Corporation vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), Local 1371, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- 78-113 Inland Steel Container Corporation vs. Chemical Workers International, Local 659, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  1/79. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 78-114 Texaco Incorporated vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-623, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  1/79. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-115 Mamaroneck Teachers Association vs. Mamaroneck Board of Education, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  12/78. Routine Correspondence. Issue: Withdrawn
- 78-116 Patrolmen's Benevolent Association vs. OMLRB (Box 27, Folder 23)
  n.d., empty folder.
- 78-117 Strick Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 816, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  11/79. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 78-118 Whippany Paper Board Company vs. United Paperworkers Union, Local 1295, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  12/27/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Fights and Altercations.
- 78-119 Otis Elevator Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), Local 989, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  4/23/79. (No Award), Transcripts, Exhibits, Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents. Issue: Arbitrability--Contract Interpretation.
- 79-121 International Silver Company vs. United Steelworkers, Local 7770, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  6/18/79. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Transcripts, Exhibits. Issue: Suspension--Drugs--Sale
- 79-122 Professional Staff Association vs. New York State United Teachers, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  9/79. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Supporting Documents. Issue: Fringe Benefits--Meal Allowance--Rates of Pay.
- 79-123 State of New York vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1979 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  5/79. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 79-124 State of New York Office of Mental Retardation, Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1979 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  7/2/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Verbal Disrespect.
- 79-125 Roosevelt Board of Education vs. Roosevelt Teachers Association, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  4/30/79. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Rates of Pay--Temporary Employee.
- 79-126 H.O. Penn Machinery Company, Incorporated vs. International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 15C, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  4/79. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 79-127 City of New York Police Department vs. Policemen's Benevolent Association, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  4/14/80. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Fringe Benefits--Health and Welfare Programs
- 79-128 Wickham Construction Company, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 363, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  8/79. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 79-129 Transworld Airlines vs. Air Line Pilots Association (ALPA), 1979 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  1/79. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 79-129a Office of Municipal Labor Relations vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  5/22/79. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Suspension--Absences--Tardiness.
- 79-130 Middlesex General Hospital vs. United Paperworkers International, Professional Nurses and Hospital Personnel, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  11/23/79. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Reinstatement--Leaves of Absence; Promotion--Rates of Pay; Overtime--Computation; Leaves of Absence--Funeral Leave--Rates of Pay.
- 79-131 Ward Foods vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 194, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  6/13/79. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Rates of Pay -- Commissions.
- 79-132 Waterview Intermediate Care and Nursing vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  7/12/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Claim for Pay of Higher Classification--Temporary Assignment.
- 79-133 Anheuser-Busch Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 102, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  8/10/79. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Exhibits, Supporting Documents. Issue: Discharge--Fights and Altercations.
- 79-134 Owens-Illinois Lily Division vs. Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 447, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  4/30/79. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Job--Rates of Pay.
- 79-135 Exxon Research and Engineering Company and Independent Laboratory Employees Union (Box 28, Folder 16)
  empty folder
- 79-136 Kendall Company vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Local 642, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  1/79. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 79-138 Hebrew National Kosher Foods Incorporated vs. Butchers, Food Handlers and Allied Workers Union, Local 174, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  6/6/79. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Rates of Pay--Holidays.
- 79-139 Veterans Administration Hospital vs. American Federation of Government Employees, Local 2094, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  5/16/79. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Incompetence and Inefficiency--Unsatisfactory Work.
- 79-140 U.S. Department of Labor vs. American Federation of Government Employees, Local 2513, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  6/27/79. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Supporting Documents. Issue: Rates of Pay--Standards of Production.
- 79-141 R.H. Macy and Company, Incorporated vs. Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, Local 1-s, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  5/28/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Discharge--Improper Job Attitude--Standards of Production--Substandard Performance
- 79-142 St. Mary's Hospital vs. Service Employees International Union, Local 144, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  8/17/79. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge--Absences, Excessive.
- 79-143 New Jersey State vs. State Troopers NCO (Non-Commissioned Officers'?) Association, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- 79-144 New Jersey State (Trenton State College) vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  6/18/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Hiring--Temporary Employees.
- 79-145 Cities Service Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, District 9, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  6/11/79. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge--Absences, excessive--Tardiness.
- 79-146 State of New Jersey vs. State Troopers Fraternal Association (STFA), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  4/79. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 79-147 State of New Jersey vs. State Troopers Fraternal Association (STFA), 1974 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- 79-148 State of New Jersey vs. State Troopers Fraternal Association (STFA), 1980 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  5/17/80. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Vacations--Seniority; Arbitrability.
- 79-149 Transworld Airlines vs. Air Line Pilots Association, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  11/5/79. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Discharge--Absences, excessive.
- 79-150 Owens-Illinois Incorporated vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 300, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  8/3/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment Outside Work Area.
- 79-151 U.S. Metals Refining Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 837, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  8/1/79. Routine Correspondence. Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
- 79-152 WF and John Barnes-Roseland Plant vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), Lodge 15, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  7/26/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Layoff--Seniority
- 79-153 Inland Steel Container Corporation vs. Chemical Workers Local 659, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  10/79. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 79-154 Brookhaven National Laboratory vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), Local 2230, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  7/12/79. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Bargaining Units--Authority of Arbitrator
- 79-155 Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 202, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  10/16/79. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Suspension--Standards of Production--Failure To Meet
- 79-156 City of New York vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District 37, Local 1549, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  6/13/79. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Fringe Benefits
- 79-157 State of New Jersey vs. State Troopers Fraternal Association (STFA), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  6/79. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 79-158 Middlesex General Hospital vs. Professional Nurses and Hospital Personnel, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  10/79. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 79-158 Tenneco Chemicals Incorporated vs. International Chemical Workers Union, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  9/6/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Improper Job Attitude--Sleeping on the Job.
- 79-160 State of New York Office of Mental Retardation vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  10/23/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Timeliness--Answer To Grievance.
- 79-161 State of New Jersey vs. New Jersey State Federation of Teachers (NJSFT), American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  6/79. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 79-162 State of New Jersey vs. Local 195, International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  10/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Rates of Pay--Call-In Emergency.
- 79-163 State of New Jersey vs. New Jersey State Troopers Fraternal Association, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  7/31/79. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Evaluation of Job Factors--Improper Evaluation.
- 79-164 State New Jersey vs. State Troopers Fraternal Association, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- 79-165 State of New Jersey vs. State Troopers Fraternal Association, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  10/10/79. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Transcripts, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Fringe Benefits--Health and Welfare Programs.
- 79-167 U.S. Postal Service vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  7/25/79. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Absences--Unauthorized
- 79-168-1 U.S. Postal Service vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Local 6000, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  7/25/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits. Issue: Discipline--Insubordination.
- 79-168-2 New York City vs. Patrolmen's Benevolent Association (PBA), 1981 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  8/19/81. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Transcripts, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Schedules of Work--Seniority--Shift Scheduling.
- 79-169 Hirsch and Cooper vs. Directors Guild of America, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  10/29/79. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 79-170 Newburgh Board of Education vs. Newburgh Teachers Association, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  11/1/79. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Leaves of Absence--Reinstatement--Promotion.
- 79-171 State of New York Office of Mental Health vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  11/79. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 79-172 City of New York Office of Municipal Labor Relations vs. Local 306, International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  9/22/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Discharge--Unsatisfactory Work--Disloyalty--Theft
- 79-173 U.S. Postal Service vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  7/79. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 79-174 Professional Staff Association vs. New York State United Teachers, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  9/79. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 79-175 Johnson and Johnson vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers, Local 1528, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  7/79. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 79-176 Menorah Home and Hospital vs. Service Employees International Union, Local 144, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  9/13/79. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Promotion--Failure to Qualify.
- 79-177 New York City Health and Hospital Corporation vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Local 1549, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  10/17/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discipline--Unauthorized Use of Company Property.
- 79-178 New York City Off-Track Betting Corporation vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Local 2021, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  8/15/79. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment to Work Outside Classification
- 79-179 Trans World Air Lines vs. Air Line Pilots Association, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- 79-180 City of New York vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  8/15/79. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits. Impasse decision.
- 79-181 U.S. Postal Service vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch #60, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  9/7/79. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Suspension--Absences--Unauthorized.
- 79-182 US Postal Service vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Local 3540, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  9/13/79. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Suspension-Insubordination--Drinking on the Job
- 79-183 United Press International vs. Wire Service Guild, Local 222, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  10/79. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 79-184 Cooper Alloy Corporation vs. International Molders and Foundry Workers, Local 81, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  10/25/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Vacation Pay.
- 79-185 New York City Police Department vs. Patrolmen's Benevolent Association, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  4/23/80. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Arbitration Procedure--Order of Producing Evidence
- 79-186 City of New York vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Local 372, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  12/12/79. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Fringe Benefits--Health and Welfare Programs
- 79-187 American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 868, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  10/3/79. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Contract Interpretation--Assignment of Jobs--Change in Location.
- 79-188 U.S. Postal Service vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  11/9/79. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Supporting Documents. Issue: Discharge--Insubordination
- 79-189 New York State Department of Correctional Services vs. Security and Law Enforcement Council 82, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  6/80. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 79-190 State of New Jersey vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  10/15/79. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Leave of Absence--Rates of Pay.
- 79-191 New York City vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District 37, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  9/79. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 79-192 New Jersey State vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  10/23/79. (No Award), Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Strikes, Slowdowns--Payment of Wages for Lost Time
- 79-193 City of New York vs. Police Benevolent Association, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  6/9/80. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Schedules of Work--Time Off Schedules
- 79-194 C.W. Post Center, Long Island University vs. C.W. Post Collegial Federation, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  10/27/80. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Probationary Employees--Termination of Employment
- 79-195 U.S. Postal Service vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 16)